

# NGO VAN TRUNG

+84 94 612 9294 | trung2601.it@gmail.com | github.com/TrungNgoVan

#### **ABOUT ME**

I'm Trung, a third-year Mathematics and Computer Science major at VNUHCM - University Of Science. I'm passionate about programming and technology. I have experience working on several real projects. I am particularly interested in becoming a Backend Developer. I have strong self-study and time management skills to help me achieve this goal.

## **EDUCATION**

BSC IN COMPUTER SCIENCE & MATHEMATICS University of Science, VNU-HCM | GPA: 7.5/10 (Semester 5/8)

## **SKILLS**

#### **Programming:**

- Language: C/C++, JavaScript, NodeJS, Go
- Knowledge: OOP, DSA, Security, Network
- Database: MongoDB, MySQL, Redis
- Project versioning: Git
- API development: Postman, Insomnia

#### Other:

- Communication
- Leadership

#### **ACCOMPLISHMENTS**

- 2023
  - Top 20 GDSC HACKATHON VIETNAM 2023 (Role Backend)
- 2022
  - Top 238 Shopee Code League.
  - o Top 5 HCMUS Student Competition with ASEAN Information Security
  - Top 10 mentor YOUPRENEUR LAUNCHPAD 2022.
- 2021
  - o Champion "Đi tìm thủ lĩnh HCMUS 2021"
- 2018
  - Silver medal at the Informatics Olympiad in Dak Lak province.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **BACKEND SOFTWARE ASSOCIATE**

Google Developer Student Clubs Chapter HCMUS
12/2022 - 9/2023

#### **MENTOR**

- Mentor 2 startup projects in Youpreneur Launchpad 2022.
- Support ideas, technology tools for project implementation

| 5/2022 - 8/2022

#### **TEACHING ASSISTANT**

- Kmin Academy Học viện khoa học máy tính
- Basic Javascript, C++, Typescript classes

| 2/2022 - 8/2023

#### **MEMBER**

- PiMA Projects in Mathematics and Applications
- Contribute an article about "Dynamic programming" on fanpage

| 9/2021 - 3/2023

## **PROJECTS**

## **Project Student Manager System**

- Use C++, knowledge of OOP and data structure.
- Basic CRUD app for managing students' info in universities

## **Project Authentication API**

- Use ExpressJS, MongoDB
- Use JWT authentication for user authentication and authorization.
- Use Bcryptjs for password encoding and decoding

## Blog "Sổ tay của Henry"

- Built with <u>Hugo</u>.
- . Blog about my algorithm, technology, experience in the field of programming

# **Morning Basket**

- Role: Backend NodeJS (main)
- Use Javascript, ReactJS, MongoDB
- Use knowledge of authenticate, database, design e-commerce API.